[
{"question":"Why we use this tag<!--...-->","right_answer":"Defines a comment"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<!DOCTYPE>","right_answer":"Defines the document type"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<a>","right_answer":"Defines a hyperlink"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<abbr>","right_answer":"Defines an abbreviation or an acronym"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<abbr>","right_answer":" instead.Defines an acronym"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<address>","right_answer":"Defines contact information for the author/owner of a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<object>","right_answer":" instead.Defines an embedded applet"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<area>","right_answer":"Defines an area inside an image map"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<article>","right_answer":"Defines an article"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<aside>","right_answer":"Defines content aside from the page content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<audio>","right_answer":"Defines embedded sound content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<b>","right_answer":"Defines bold text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<base>","right_answer":"Specifies the base URL/target for all relative URLs in a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<bdi>","right_answer":"Isolates a part of text that might be formatted in a different direction from other text outside it"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<bdo>","right_answer":"Overrides the current text direction"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<blockquote>","right_answer":"Defines a section that is quoted from another source"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<body>","right_answer":"Defines the document's body"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<br>","right_answer":"Defines a single line break"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<button>","right_answer":"Defines a clickable button"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<canvas>","right_answer":"Used to draw graphics"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<caption>","right_answer":"Defines a table caption"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<cite>","right_answer":"Defines the title of a work"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<code>","right_answer":"Defines a piece of computer code"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<col>","right_answer":"Specifies column properties for each column within a "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<colgroup>","right_answer":" element "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<colgroup>","right_answer":"Specifies a group of one or more columns in a table for formatting"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<data>","right_answer":"Adds a machine-readable translation of a given content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<datalist>","right_answer":"Specifies a list of pre-defined options for input controls"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<dd>","right_answer":"Defines a description/value of a term in a description list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<del>","right_answer":"Defines text that has been deleted from a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<details>","right_answer":"Defines additional details that the user can view or hide"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<dfn>","right_answer":"Specifies a term that is going to be defined within the content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<dialog>","right_answer":"Defines a dialog box or window"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<ul>","right_answer":" instead.Defines a directory list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<div>","right_answer":"Defines a section in a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<dl>","right_answer":"Defines a description list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<dt>","right_answer":"Defines a term/name in a description list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<em>","right_answer":"Defines emphasized text "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<embed>","right_answer":"Defines a container for an external application"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<fieldset>","right_answer":"Groups related elements in a form"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<figcaption>","right_answer":"Defines a caption for a "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<figure>","right_answer":" element"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<figure>","right_answer":"Specifies self-contained content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<footer>","right_answer":"Defines a footer for a document or section"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<form>","right_answer":"Defines an HTML form for user input"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<h1>","right_answer":" to Defines HTML headings use one time in page "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<h6>","right_answer":" Defines HTML headings with size 6"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<head>","right_answer":"Contains metadata/information for the document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<header>","right_answer":"Defines a header for a document or section"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<hr>","right_answer":" Defines a thematic change in the content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<html>","right_answer":"Defines the root of an HTML document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<i>","right_answer":"Defines a part of text in an alternate voice or mood"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<iframe>","right_answer":"Defines an inline frame"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<img>","right_answer":"Defines an image"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<input>","right_answer":"Defines an input control"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<ins>","right_answer":"Defines a text that has been inserted into a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<kbd>","right_answer":"Defines keyboard input"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<label>","right_answer":"Defines a label for an "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<input>","right_answer":" element"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<legend>","right_answer":"Defines a caption for a "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<fieldset>","right_answer":" element"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<li>","right_answer":"Defines a list item"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<link>","right_answer":"Defines the relationship between a document and an external resource (most used to link to style sheets)"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<main>","right_answer":"Specifies the main content of a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<map>","right_answer":"Defines an image map"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<mark>","right_answer":"Defines marked/highlighted text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<meta>","right_answer":"Defines metadata about an HTML document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<meter>","right_answer":"Defines a scalar measurement within a known range (a gauge)"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<nav>","right_answer":"Defines navigation links"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<object>","right_answer":"Defines a container for an external application"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<ol>","right_answer":"Defines an ordered list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<optgroup>","right_answer":"Defines a group of related options in a drop-down list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<option>","right_answer":"Defines an option in a drop-down list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<output>","right_answer":"Defines the result of a calculation"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<p>","right_answer":"Defines a paragraph"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<param>","right_answer":"Defines a parameter for an object"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<picture>","right_answer":"Defines a container for multiple image resources"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<pre>","right_answer":"Defines preformatted text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<progress>","right_answer":"Represents the progress of a task"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<q>","right_answer":"Defines a short quotation"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<rt>","right_answer":"Defines an explanation/pronunciation of characters (for East Asian typography)"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<ruby>","right_answer":"Defines a ruby annotation (for East Asian typography)"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<s>","right_answer":"Defines text that is no longer correct"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<samp>","right_answer":"Defines sample output from a computer program"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<script>","right_answer":"Defines a client-side script"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<section>","right_answer":"Defines a section in a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<select>","right_answer":"Defines a drop-down list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<small>","right_answer":"Defines smaller text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<s>","right_answer":" instead.Defines strikethrough text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<strong>","right_answer":"Defines important text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<style>","right_answer":"Defines style information for a document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<sub>","right_answer":"Defines subscripted text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<summary>","right_answer":"Defines a visible heading for a "},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<details>","right_answer":" element"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<sup>","right_answer":"Defines superscripted text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<svg>","right_answer":"Defines a container for SVG graphics"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<table>","right_answer":"Defines a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<tbody>","right_answer":"Groups the body content in a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<td>","right_answer":"Defines a cell in a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<template>","right_answer":"Defines a container for content that should be hidden when the page loads"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<textarea>","right_answer":"Defines a multiline input control (text area)"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<tfoot>","right_answer":"Groups the footer content in a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<th>","right_answer":"Defines a header cell in a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<thead>","right_answer":"Groups the header content in a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<time>","right_answer":"Defines a specific time (or datetime)"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<title>","right_answer":"Defines a title for the document"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<tr>","right_answer":"Defines a row in a table"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<u>","right_answer":"Defines some text that is unarticulated and styled differently from normal text"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<ul>","right_answer":"Defines an unordered list"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<var>","right_answer":"Defines a variable"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<video>","right_answer":"Defines embedded video content"},
{"question":"Why we use this tag<wbr>","right_answer":"Defines a possible line-break"}
]